A Guide to the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records FA017
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Scholars and Visiting Fellows, 1983-1998; 1
  - Scholar Applicants, 1983-1998; 1
    - Denied Applicants, 1984-1990; B
      - Brothers, Leslie - Application 860023 (Reel 37, Frame 410)
      - Sherris, David - Application 860024 (Reel 37, Frame 443)
      - Murphy, Kenneth M. M. - Application 860025 (Reel 37, Frame 471)
      - Horton, Teresa H. - Application 860026 (Reel 37, Frame 507)
      - Aronow, Bruce J. - Application 860027 (Reel 37, Frame 539)
      - Dang, Chi V. - Application 860028 (Reel 37, Frame 570)
      - Wolin, Sandra L. - Application 860029 (Reel 37, Frame 609)
      - Bearer, Elaine L. - Application 860030 (Reel 37, Frame 637)
      - Palackal, Thomas - Application 860032 (Reel 37, Frame 679)
      - Matthews, Barbara G. - Application 860034 (Reel 37, Frame 704)
      - Herzog, Norbert K. - Application 860036 (Reel 37, Frame 739)
      - Roach, Deborah A. - Application 860037 (Reel 37, Frame 776)
      - Triezenberg, Stephen J. - Application 860038 (Reel 37, Frame 806)
      - Costanzo, Maria C. - Application 860039 (Reel 37, Frame 835)
      - Broek, Daniel - Application 860040 (Reel 37, Frame 868)
      - Ponder, Jay W. - Application 860043 (Reel 37, Frame 899)
      - Palmer, Jeffrey M. - Application 860044 (Reel 37, Frame 929)
      - Watowich, Stanley J. J. - Application 860045 (Reel 37, Frame 965)
      - Carley, DAvid W. - Application 860046 (Reel 37, Frame 1000)
      - Miller, Larry R. - Application 860047 (Reel 37, Frame 1029)
      - Archer, Stephen L. - Application 860048 (Reel 37, Frame 1060)
      - Worman, Howard J. - Application 860049 (Reel 37, Frame 1098)
      - Anderson, Ted L. - Application 860050 (Reel 37, Frame 1132)
      - Hazen-Martin, Debra J. - Application 860051 (Reel 37, Frame 1169)
      - Johnston, David E. - Application 860052 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
      - Lonberg, Nils - Application 860053 (Reel 38, Frame 37)
      - Loftus, Joseph C. - Application 860054 (Reel 38, Frame 67)
      - Seifert, H. Steven - Application 860055 (Reel 38, Frame 106)
      - Way, Jeffrey C. - Application 860056 (Reel 38, Frame 139)
      - Mawe, Gary M. - Application 860057 (Reel 38, Frame 168)
      - Julius, David J. - Application 860058 (Reel 38, Frame 200)
      - Nuovo, Gerard J. - Application 860059 (Reel 38, Frame 233)
      - Maihle, Nita J. - Application 860060 (Reel 38, Frame 252)
      - Gauthier, V. Joyce - Application 860061 (Reel 38, Frame 285)
      - Olwin, Bradley B. - Application 860062 (Reel 38, Frame 318)
      - Atchison, Michael L. - Application 860063 (Reel 38, Frame 351)
      - Kardon, Randy H. - Application 860064 (Reel 38, Frame 384)
      - Caldwell, Jack D. - Application 860065 (Reel 38, Frame 422)
      - Knisley, Keith A. - Application 860066 (Reel 38, Frame 460)
      - Ziai, Mohammad R. - Application 860067 (Reel 38, Frame 490)
      - Andy, Robin J. - Application 860068 (Reel 38, Frame 520)
      - Schofield, Daniel L. - Application 860069 (Reel 38, Frame 550)
      - Nahum, Avi - Application 860070 (Reel 38, Frame 584)
      - Gulig, Paul A. - Application 860071 (Reel 38, Frame 622)
      - Marcantonio, Eugene E. - Application 860072 (Reel 38, Frame 658)
      - Laher, Ismael - Application 860074 (Reel 38, Frame 691)
      - Silberstein, David S. - Application 860075 (Reel 38, Frame 728)
      - Ingber, Donald E. - Application 860076 (Reel 38, Frame 757)
      - Jay, Daniel G. - Application 860077 (Reel 38, Frame 790)
      - Crane, John K. - Application 860079 (Reel 38, Frame 822)
      - Campbell, Michael J. - Application 860080 (Reel 38, Frame 861)
      - Seaholtz, Audrey F. - Application 860081 (Reel 38, Frame 894)
      - Huber, Klaus - Application 860082 (Reel 38, Frame 924)
      - Knapp, Andrew G. - Application 860084 (Reel 38, Frame 958)
      - Ronnett, Gabriele V. - Application 860085 (Reel 38, Frame 991)
      - Gurri-Glass, Gregory E. - Application 860086 (Reel 38, Frame 1025)
      - Hildreth, James E. - Application 860087 (Reel 38, Frame 1063)
      - Semenkovich, Clay F. - Application 860088 (Reel 38, Frame 1097)
      - Shiffman, Mitchell L. - Application 860089 (Reel 38, Frame 1132)
      - Skubitz, Amy P. N. - Application 860090 (Reel 38, Frame 1171)
      - Hsia, Judith A. - Application 860091 (Reel 39, Frame 1)
      - Thomas, Gerald A. - Application 860092 (Reel 39, Frame 33)
      - Cole, Judith A. - Application 860093 (Reel 39, Frame 59)
      - Davidson, Daniel B. - Application 860094 (Reel 39, Frame 91)
      - Alila, Hector W. - Application 860095 (Reel 39, Frame 119)
      - Swiedler, Stuart J. - Application 860096 (Reel 39, Frame 149)
      - Hagedorn, Mary M. - Application 860098 (Reel 39, Frame 178)
      - Hoder, Sally L. - Application 860099 (Reel 39, Frame 207)
      - Van Wagoner, David R. - Application 860100 (Reel 39, Frame 242)
      - Adamski, Stan - Application 860101 (Reel 39, Frame 270)
      - Eskenazi, Allen E. - Application 860102 (Reel 39, Frame 301)
      - Menon-Unni, Latha K. - Application 860103 (Reel 39, Frame 328)
      - Anderson, James M. - Application 860104 (Reel 39, Frame 356)
      - Lasser, Andrew - Application 860105 (Reel 39, Frame 390)
      - Brown, Laura - Application 860106 (Reel 39, Frame 392)
      - Jones, Terrell E. - Application 860107 (Reel 39, Frame 428)
      - Damtew, Belai - Application 860108 (Reel 39, Frame 460)
      - Seyfred, Mark A. - Application 860109 (Reel 39, Frame 494)
      - Balczon, Ronald D. - Application 860110 (Reel 39, Frame 527)
      - Carroll, Sean B. - Application 860111 (Reel 39, Frame 558)
      - Lai, Eseng - Application 860112 (Reel 39, Frame 589)
      - Adams, Richard J. - Application 860114 (Reel 39, Frame 623)
      - Fister, Richard D. - Application 860115 (Reel 39, Frame 652)
      - Lieberman, Judy - Application 860116 (Reel 39, Frame 679)
      - Makino, Shinji - Application 860117 (Reel 39, Frame 707)
      - Wiens, Darrell - Application 860118 (Reel 39, Frame 745)
      - Jacob, Chaim O. - Application 860119 (Reel 39, Frame 778)
      - Teem, John L. - Application 860120 (Reel 39, Frame 812)
      - Koomey, J. Michael - Application 860121 (Reel 39, Frame 842)
      - Peris, Joanna - Application 860122 (Reel 39, Frame 873)
      - Wolf, Robert A. - Application 860123 (Reel 39, Frame 908)
      - McCune, Joseph M. - Application 860124 (Reel 39, Frame 938)
      - Squier, Thomas C. - Application 860125 (Reel 39, Frame 977)
      - Fox, Susan R. - Application 860127 (Reel 39, Frame 1007)
      - Yother, Janet L. - Application 860128 (Reel 39, Frame 1039)
      - DiPersio, John F. - Application 860129 (Reel 39, Frame 1077)
      - Aprison, Barry S. - Application 860130 (Reel 39, Frame 1115)
      - Corvera, Silvia - Application 860131 (Reel 39, Frame 1146)
      - Pederson, Steen E. - Application 860132 (Reel 39, Frame 1175)
      - Balaban, Evan S. - Application 860133 (Reel 39, Frame 1204)
      - Wallis, Robert S. - Application 860134 (Reel 40, Frame 1)
      - Schuster, Stephen J. - Application 860135 (Reel 40, Frame 30)
      - Wendelborn, Daniel F. - Application 860136 (Reel 40, Frame 62)
      - Hall, Frederick L. - Application 860137 (Reel 40, Frame 91)
      - Schreiber, Steven S. - Application 860138 (Reel 40, Frame 121)
      - Frey, Alan B. - Application 860139 (Reel 40, Frame 149)
      - Hortin, Glen L. - Application 860140 (Reel 40, Frame 179)
      - Ahrens, Helga - Application 860141 (Reel 40, Frame 216)
      - Erickson, Jan S. - Application 860142 (Reel 40, Frame 248)
      - Beauchamp, Robert D. - Application 860143 (Reel 40, Frame 279)
      - Spiegel, Katharyn - Application 860144 (Reel 40, Frame 317)
      - Kolp, Lisa A. - Application 860145 (Reel 40, Frame 350)
      - Gottschall, Paul E. - Application 860146 (Reel 40, Frame 383)
      - Demer, Linda L. - Application 860147 (Reel 40, Frame 418)
      - Hemmings, Hugh C., Jr. - Application 860148 (Reel 40, Frame 453)
      - Wood, Nelson - Application 860149 (Reel 40, Frame 489)
      - Kenney, Shannon C. - Application 860150 (Reel 40, Frame 515)
      - Deretic, Vojo - Application 860151 (Reel 40, Frame 549)
      - Ziegler, Steven F. - Application 860152 (Reel 40, Frame 584)
      - Gore, Ira, Jr. - Application 860153 (Reel 40, Frame 614)
      - Truemper, Edward J. - Application 860154 (Reel 40, Frame 649)
      - Hahn, Steven M. - Application 860155 (Reel 40, Frame 680)
      - Kalaria, Rajesh N. - Application 860156 (Reel 40, Frame 703)
      - Canada, Andrew T. - Application 860157 (Reel 40, Frame 740)
      - Carlisle, Joseph T. - Application 860158 (Reel 40, Frame 775)
      - Silva-Lopez, Edibaldo - Application 860159 (Reel 40, Frame 809)
      - McCormick, David A. - Application 860160 (Reel 40, Frame 835)
      - Bowser, Samuel S. - Application 860161 (Reel 40, Frame 869)
      - Teragawa, Carolyn K. - Application 860162 (Reel 40, Frame 904)
      - Sundstrom, Paula M. - Application 860164 (Reel 40, Frame 933)
      - Smith, Mark A. - Application 860165 (Reel 40, Frame 961)
      - Kashtan, Clifford E. - Application 860166 (Reel 40, Frame 995)
      - Berlin, Joshua R. - Application 860167 (Reel 40, Frame 1028)
      - Hock, Randy - Application 860168 (Reel 40, Frame 1060)
      - Hearing, Janet C. - Application 860169 (Reel 40, Frame 1097)
      - Eberwine, James - Application 860170 (Reel 40, Frame 1127)
      - Hoffmann, Susan T. - Application 860171 (Reel 40, Frame 1159)
      - Davis, Trisha N. - Application 860173 (Reel 40, Frame 1193)
      - Wahlstrom, Hakan E. - Application 860174 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
      - Gordon, Karen - Application 860175 (Reel 41, Frame 29)
      - Kalir, Henry H. - Application 860176 (Reel 41, Frame 60)
      - Kayar, Susan R. - Application 860177 (Reel 41, Frame 90)
      - Miller, Alan M. - Application 860178 (Reel 41, Frame 124)
      - Willing, Marcia C. - Application 870002 (Reel 41, Frame 159)
      - Duffy, Linda C. - Application 870003 (Reel 41, Frame 193)
      - Brennan, Richard G. - Application 870004 (Reel 41, Frame 224)
      - Ramoa, Ary S. S. - Application 870005 (Reel 41, Frame 258)
      - Christenson, Ware R. - Application 870006 (Reel 41, Frame 295)
      - Waldow, Stephen M. - Application 870007 (Reel 41, Frame 327)
      - Hecht, Michael H. - Application 870008 (Reel 41, Frame 356)
      - Beachy, Philip A. - Application 870009 (Reel 41, Frame 384)
      - Weinert, Ted A. - Application 870011 (Reel 41, Frame 414)
      - King, Thomas C. - Application 870013 (Reel 41, Frame 444)
      - Manaker, Scott - Application 870015 (Reel 41, Frame 484)
      - Stelzer, Armin - Application 870016 (Reel 41, Frame 524)
      - Lee, Gwo-Shu M. - Application 870017 (Reel 41, Frame 562)
      - Smith, Theodore A. G. - Application 870018 (Reel 41, Frame 595)
      - Hughes, Kelly T. - Application 870019 (Reel 41, Frame 627)
      - Gnadt, James W. - Application 870020 (Reel 41, Frame 654)
      - Densmore, Mary A. - Application 870022 (Reel 41, Frame 691)
      - Gilmour, David S. - Application 870023 (Reel 41, Frame 717)
      - Tillinghast, Jeffrey P. - Application 870025 (Reel 41, Frame 750)
      - Murphy, Kenneth M. M. - Application 870026 (Reel 41, Frame 781)
      - Hyson, Richard L. - Application 870027 (Reel 41, Frame 825)
      - Saul, Jerome P. - Application 870028 (Reel 41, Frame 863)
      - Bischoff, Joyce E. - Application 870029 (Reel 41, Frame 897)
      - DuBois, Raymond N. - Application 870030 (Reel 41, Frame 930)
      - Patterson, Jan. E. - Application 870032 (Reel 41, Frame 962)
      - Crane, John K. - Application 870033 (Reel 41, Frame 1001)
      - Ponder, Stephen W. - Application 870034 (Reel 41, Frame 1043)
      - Owen, Mary J. H. - Application 870035 (Reel 41, Frame 1073)
      - Wolfman, Alan - Application 870036 (Reel 41, Frame 1108)
      - Herman, James P. - Application 870038 (Reel 41, Frame 1138)
      - Adamski, Stan W. - Application 870039 (Reel 41, Frame 1173)
      - Bos, Timothy J. - Application 870040 (Reel 41, Frame 1207)
      - Rosenberg, Susan M. - Application 870041 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
      - Gray, D. Bruce - Application 870042 (Reel 42, Frame 27)
      - Omara-Alwala, Thomas R. - Application 870043 (Reel 42, Frame 52)
      - Housley, Gary D. - Application 870044 (Reel 42, Frame 68)
      - Maxwell, Steven A. - Application 870045 (Reel 42, Frame 106)
      - Haracz, John L. - Application 870046 (Reel 42, Frame 138)
      - Kerr, Joanne T. - Application 870047 (Reel 42, Frame 174)
      - Goldenring, James R. - Application 870048 (Reel 42, Frame 203)
      - Ganea, Doina - Application 870049 (Reel 42, Frame 244)
      - Mayne, Katherine M. - Application 870050 (Reel 42, Frame 289)
      - Thompson, Kent N. - Application 870051 (Reel 42, Frame 320)
      - Vera, Pedro L. - Application 870052 (Reel 42, Frame 346)
      - Van Voorhis, Wesley C. - Application 870053 (Reel 42, Frame 380)
      - Omary, M. Bishr - Application 870054 (Reel 42, Frame 415)
      - Bertram, Edward H., III - Application 870055 (Reel 42, Frame 451)
      - McLeod, Kenneth J. - Application 870056 (Reel 42, Frame 488)
      - Beck, Melinda A. - Application 870057 (Reel 42, Frame 521)
      - Till, Mark - Application 870058 (Reel 42, Frame 550)
      - West, Susan E. H. - Application 870060 (Reel 42, Frame 580)
      - Horne, William H. - Application 870061 (Reel 42, Frame 614)
      - Millhauser, Glenn L. - Application 870062 (Reel 42, Frame 646)
      - Fisher, Douglas A. - Application 870063 (Reel 42, Frame 677)
      - Alila, Hector W. - Application 870064 (Reel 42, Frame 705)
      - Brown, Theodore J. - Application 870065 (Reel 42, Frame 738)
      - Beaubien, Beatrice C. - Application 870067 (Reel 42, Frame 774)
      - Lucas, Jen H. - Application 870068 (Reel 42, Frame 805)
      - Doeller, Jeannette E. - Application 870069 (Reel 42, Frame 842)
      - Tobet, Stuart A. - Application 870070 (Reel 42, Frame 876)
      - Horowitz, Stuart - Application 870071 (Reel 42, Frame 911)
      - Orlowski, Janis M. - Application 870072 (Reel 42, Frame 942)
      - Katzman, Michael - Application 870073 (Reel 42, Frame 984)
      - Light, Douglas B. - Application 870074 (Reel 42, Frame 1020)
      - Lerner, Laura - Application 870075 (Reel 42, Frame 1052)
      - Dillon, Susan B. - Application 870076 (Reel 42, Frame 1107)
      - Roos, David S. - Application 870077 (Reel 42, Frame 1147)
      - Duffy, Charles J. - Application 870078 (Reel 42, Frame 1184)
      - Crawford, James M. - Application 870081 (Reel 43, Frame 1)
      - Wolfe, Alan J. - Application 870082 (Reel 43, Frame 44)
      - Griffiths, Gillian M. - Application 870083 (Reel 43, Frame 72)
      - van de Rijn, Jan M. - Application 870084 (Reel 43, Frame 103)
      - McConnell, Susan K. - Application 870085 (Reel 43, Frame 133)
      - Shuster, Michael J. - Application 870086 (Reel 43, Frame 170)
      - Matson, David O. - Application 870087 (Reel 43, Frame 204)
      - Wolf, Karen M. - Application 870088 (Reel 43, Frame 247)
      - Jasin, Maria - Application 870089 (Reel 43, Frame 281)
      - Kiel, Jeffrey W. - Application 870090 (Reel 43, Frame 310)
      - Ch'ng, John L. C. - Application 870091 (Reel 43, Frame 339)
      - Samuels, Mark E. - Application 870092 (Reel 43, Frame 370)
      - Klein, Bruce S. - Application 870093 (Reel 43, Frame 399)
      - Kuzmanoff, Konrad M. - Application 870094 (Reel 43, Frame 443)
      - Stone, Charles K. - Application 870095 (Reel 43, Frame 474)
      - Russo, Paul - Application 870096 (Reel 43, Frame 506)
      - Bristow, Cynthia L. - Application 870098 (Reel 43, Frame 539)
      - Yankelevich, Boris - Application 870099 (Reel 43, Frame 567)
      - Lovell, Mark A. - Application 870101 (Reel 43, Frame 595)
      - Lai, Eseng - Application 870102 (Reel 43, Frame 626)
      - Kernstine, Kemp H. - Application 870103 (Reel 43, Frame 656)
      - Oswald, C. Brent - Application 870104 (Reel 43, Frame 689)
      - Silver, Randi B. - Application 870105 (Reel 43, Frame 725)
      - Stork, Philip J. S. - Application 870106 (Reel 43, Frame 756)
      - Byrd, Thomas F., III - Application 870107 (Reel 43, Frame 783)
      - Green, Kerry P. - Application 870108 (Reel 43, Frame 814)
      - Runge, Kurt W. - Application 870109 (Reel 43, Frame 846)
      - Bass, Brenda L. - Application 870110 (Reel 43, Frame 875)
      - Mitchell, Pamela J. - Application 870111 (Reel 43, Frame 904)
      - Lawrance, Simon K. - Application 870112 (Reel 43, Frame 935)
      - Nusbaum, Michael P. - Application 870113 (Reel 43, Frame 970)
      - Wiest, Peter M. - Application 870114 (Reel 43, Frame 1004)
      - Abramson, Stewart N. - Application 870115 (Reel 43, Frame 1041)
      - Tausk, Francisco A. - Application 870116 (Reel 43, Frame 1072)
      - Mucke, Lennart - Application 870117 (Reel 43, Frame 1104)
      - Glushka, John N. - Application 870120 (Reel 43, Frame 1137)
      - Sherry, Barbara - Application 870121 (Reel 43, Frame 1163)
      - Cline, Hollis T. - Application 870123 (Reel 43, Frame 1191)
      - Ewing, Mary W. - Application 870124 (Reel 44, Frame 1)
      - Herzog, Nortbert K. - Application 870125 (Reel 44, Frame 27)
      - Rossie, Sandra S. - Application 870126 (Reel 44, Frame 62)
      - Ballew, Carol - Application 880001 (Reel 44, Frame 97)
      - Krause, Michael W. - Application 880002 (Reel 44, Frame 142)
      - Fowler, Walter E. - Application 880003 (Reel 44, Frame 174)
      - Bustos, Mauricio M. - Application 880004 (Reel 44, Frame 216)
      - Musser, James M. - Application 880005 (Reel 44, Frame 248)
      - Pamer, Eric G. - Application 880006 (Reel 44, Frame 287)
      - Patson, Philip - Application 880007 (Reel 44, Frame 319)
      - Turner, John R. A. - Application 880008 (Reel 44, Frame 348)
      - Hennessey, John P., Jr. - Application 880009 (Reel 44, Frame 387)
      - Till, Mark A. - Application 880010 (Reel 44, Frame 423)
      - Vathy, Ilona - Application 880011 (Reel 44, Frame 455)
      - Shah, Gul N. - Application 880012 (Reel 44, Frame 486)
      - Ferrel, James E., Jr. - Application 880015 (Reel 44, Frame 524)
      - Farr, Spencer B. - Application 880016 (Reel 44, Frame 560)
      - Grissom, Charles B. - Application 880016 (Reel 44, Frame 595)
      - Bollen, Anne-Marie - Application 880018 (Reel 44, Frame 630)
      - Germino, F. Joseph - Application 880019 (Reel 44, Frame 665)
      - Melancon-Kaplan, Johanne - Application 880020 (Reel 44, Frame 697)
      - Ralph, Martin R. - Application 880021 (Reel 44, Frame 737)
      - Rosenberg, Susan M. - Application 880022 (Reel 44, Frame 772)
      - O'Donoghue, Daniel L. - Application 880024 (Reel 44, Frame 800)
      - Kurpakus, Michelle A. - Application 880025 (Reel 44, Frame 834)
      - Malhotra, Vivek - Application 880026 (Reel 44, Frame 865)
      - Metzger, Joseph M. - Application 880027 (Reel 44, Frame 896)
      - Gilbert, Susan P. - Application 880028 (Reel 44, Frame 931)
      - Smale, Stephen T. - Application 880029 (Reel 44, Frame 966)
      - Trono, Didier - Application 880030 (Reel 44, Frame 993)
      - Blakely, Randy D. - Application 880031 (Reel 44, Frame 1021)
      - Baranski, Bruce G. - Application 880032 (Reel 44, Frame 1058)
      - Barres, Barbara A. - Application 880033 (Reel 44, Frame 1089)
      - Davenport, Robert C., Jr. - Application 880034 (Reel 44, Frame 1131)
      - Gansbacher, Bernd - Application 880035 (Reel 44, Frame 1164)
      - Lutz, Margaret - Application 880036 (Reel 44, Frame 1196)
      - Eide, David J. - Application 880039 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
      - Garcia-Blanco, Mariano A. - Application 880040 (Reel 45, Frame 31)
      - Khouri, Margaret R. - Application 880041 (Reel 45, Frame 61)
      - Samuelson, John C. - Application 880042 (Reel 45, Frame 96)
      - Makover, David - Application 880043 (Reel 45, Frame 128)
      - Stern, Michael J. - Application 880044 (Reel 45, Frame 157)
      - Jones, Gary R. - Application 880047 (Reel 45, Frame 188)
      - Kutteh, William H. - Application 880048 (Reel 45, Frame 223)
      - McDonnell, Sue M. - Application 880049 (Reel 45, Frame 265)
      - Meriney, Stephen D. - Application 880050 (Reel 45, Frame 299)
      - Thomason, Donald B. - Application 880051 (Reel 45, Frame 330)
      - Smith, Jeffrey W. - Application 880052 (Reel 45, Frame 365)
      - Chen, Thelma A. - Application 880053 (Reel 45, Frame 397)
      - Benfrey, Philip - Application 880054 (Reel 45, Frame 432)
      - Sretavan, David W. - Application 880055 (Reel 45, Frame 462)
      - Gibbs, Robert B. - Application 880056 (Reel 45, Frame 493)
      - Shtivelman, Emilia - Application 880058 (Reel 45, Frame 523)
      - Koretzky, Gary A. - Application 880059 (Reel 45, Frame 552)
      - Brow, David A. - Application 880060 (Reel 45, Frame 587)
      - Blochlinger, Karen - Application 880061 (Reel 45, Frame 617)
      - Picot, Daniel - Application 880062 (Reel 45, Frame 649)
      - Cagliero, Enrico - Application 880063 (Reel 45, Frame 680)
      - Cronmiller, Claire R. - Application 880064 (Reel 45, Frame 717)
      - Peachey, Neal S. - Application 880065 (Reel 45, Frame 747)
      - Bazinet, Christopher W. - Application 880066 (Reel 45, Frame 784)
      - Butler, Pamela D. - Application 880067 (Reel 45, Frame 815)
      - Miller, Beverly W. - Application 880069 (Reel 45, Frame 852)
      - Churchill, Laurie - Application 880070 (Reel 45, Frame 880)
      - Alles, Ajit J. - Application 880071 (Reel 45, Frame 914)
      - Byrne, Barry J. - Application 880073 (Reel 45, Frame 941)
      - Bennett, Jean - Application 880075 (Reel 45, Frame 977)
      - Talor, Eyal - Application 880076 (Reel 45, Frame 1008)
      - Abramson, Stewart N. - Application 880077 (Reel 45, Frame 1060)
      - Drugge, Elizabeth D. - Application 880078 (Reel 45, Frame 1090)
      - Carter, Thomas H. - Application 880079 (Reel 45, Frame 1119)
      - Cole, Ada H. - Application 880081 (Reel 45, Frame 1155)
      - Agura, Edward D. - Application 880082 (Reel 46, Frame 1)
      - Patterson, Thomas F. - Application 880083 (Reel 46, Frame 23)
      - Haynesworth, Stephen E. - Application 880084 (Reel 46, Frame 64)
      - Hulette, Christine M. - Application 880085 (Reel 46, Frame 95)
      - Parkman, Henry P. - Application 880086 (Reel 46, Frame 126)
      - Matshushita, Sho - Application 880087 (Reel 46, Frame 156)
      - Brown, Steven D. - Application 880088 (Reel 46, Frame 187)
      - Morley, Deborah L. - Application 880089 (Reel 46, Frame 219)
      - Kushner, Leslie J. - Application 880090 (Reel 46, Frame 252)
      - Sharp, Kim A. - Application 880091 (Reel 46, Frame 285)
      - Gao, Xiaolian - Application 880092 (Reel 46, Frame 319)
      - Sweatt, J. David - Application 880093 (Reel 46, Frame 347)
      - Paul, Jeremy I. - Application 880095 (Reel 46, Frame 382)
      - Sive, Hazel L. - Application 880096 (Reel 46, Frame 412)
      - Pilz, Renate B. - Application 880097 (Reel 46, Frame 439)
      - Chialvo, Dante R. - Application 880098 (Reel 46, Frame 470)
      - Moreb, Jan S. - Application 880099 (Reel 46, Frame 498)
      - Gilmore, Gary L. - Application 880100 (Reel 46, Frame 530)
      - Kron, Michael A. - Application 880101 (Reel 46, Frame 556)
      - McLean, Mark P. - Application 880102 (Reel 46, Frame 593)
      - Saez, Juan C. - Application 880103 (Reel 46, Frame 626)
      - Lam, Kit S. - Application 880104 (Reel 46, Frame 665)
      - Greenwald, James E. - Application 880105 (Reel 46, Frame 700)
      - Milner, Peter G. - Application 880108 (Reel 46, Frame 728)
      - Umans, Jason G. - Application 880109 (Reel 46, Frame 759)
      - Gibbs, Richard A. L. - Application 880110 (Reel 46, Frame 797)
      - Mattox, William - Application 880111 (Reel 46, Frame 830)
      - Flanigan, Timothy P. - Application 880112 (Reel 46, Frame 860)
      - Dempsey, Edward C. - Application 880113 (Reel 46, Frame 893)
      - Lev-Ram, Varda - Application 880114 (Reel 46, Frame 934)